Guide to the Philosophy of Science Association Records, 1959-2005 ASP.1992.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Biennial Meeting Papers and Symposia Submissions, 1996-2002; XV.
  - PSA 2002 (Milwaukee, WI) Accepted Symposia, 6.
    - Frisch, Mathias, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Giere, Ronald N., 2002 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Griffiths, Paul, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Grunbaum, Adolf, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Hausman, Daniel and James Woodward, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Hitchcock, Christopher, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Howard, Don, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Humphreys, Paul, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Koertge, Noretta, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Koslow, Arnold, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Mayo, Deborah G. and Aris Spanos, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - McAllister, James W., 2002 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Menzies, Peter, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Morgan, Mary S., 2002 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Morrison, Margaret, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Norton, John D., 2002 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Polger, Thomas, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Plutynski, Anya, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Rolin, Kristina, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Sargent, Mary Rose, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Sarkar, Sahorta, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Shrader-Frechette, Kristin, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Skipper Jr., Robert A., 2002 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Sklar, Lawrence, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Spirtes, Peter, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Suarez, Mauricio, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Tanona, Scott, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Teller, Paul, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - van Fraassen, Bas, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - von Eckhardt, Barbara, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Wilson, Robert A., 2002 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Winsberg, Eric, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Woody, Andrea, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Rejected Biennial Meeting Papers and Symposia Submissions, 1996-2002; 7.
    Subseries 7. contains rejected biennial meeting papers and symposia submissions, organized by submitting author's last name and received between 1996-2002
- Journal Submission Files, 1975-2004; XVI.
  Series XVI. Journal Submission Files contains submission information for articles to be published in the Journal of Scientific Philosophy. A large portion of the collection is comprised of files relating to the organization and publication of the Philosophy of Science Association Journal, including drafts, memos, correspondence, and proofs of papers. Files are organized by submission date and labeled by submitting author's name, title of the paper and the number issued to the paper by the PSA office.
  Access to paper submission files for the Journal of Scientific Philosophy is restricted for 75 years from date of submission.